The world isn't the world by accident.
Nothing developed the way it did out of
happen stance. It has been a takeover
for a very long
time. People have been sold the idea
that freedom is the ultimate thing in
life. Most people want communities,
families, and security. But we've
supplanted. We go freedom. You can have
all the jobs or none of the jobs. You
can do whatever you want and live
wherever you want. You can invest in
anything you want. Isn't it great? You
can deliver food and you can Uber and
have an Only Fans and a blog and a
podcast. You could do it all. You're a
media Anthony. You are who you've been
waiting for. You don't need anybody
else. You can go to school online or
offline or a brick and mortar, whatever
you like. It doesn't matter. You could
team up with a bunch of people and start
a YouTube channel where you review
architecture from old houses that are
now abandoned and that crackheads live
in because we ship the chocolate factory
away. You have all the freedom in the
world, but none of the security, none of
the benefits. We've given you all the
freedom, all the pretend freedom that
you wouldn't know what to do with. And
it's not designed for you to actually
use Donald
Trump. Here's the thing, and I'll get in
trouble for saying this. I don't know if
this will
work, but he's not
wrong. I don't know if it'll work, but
he's not wrong.
I passed a chocolate factory the other
day and it is silly to think about that
kind of America coming back. It's why we
started with the newsies and the this
and the that. And it is funny and it is
silly the idea of people having a job
and security. It is silly to think
about. It is funny. It is
strange. But we've given you freedom and
we've taken everything else away.
We're a scambased economy. Do I love the
Trump crypto [__] Absolutely not. Do I
love some of his new tech friends? We
know how I feel. I'm not going to be the
ad nauseium guy that annoys everybody
with
it. But I'm telling you right now, we're
selling you
freedom, but we're not really selling
you freedom. The word we're selling
you is chaos.
You're mistaking freedom for chaos. You
think that you are free to do anything
you want, but you're free to gamble.
You're free to hedge your bets. You're
free chaos, disorder,
confusion. That's what we mean by
freedom. a manic attempt to survive.
Your spiritual life, your emotional
well-being, your mental health, your
sexual health, all of these things are
suffering because you're scrambling to
survive and put money in your bank
account. But we've convinced you that
that's an actual great state of being.
That insanity, that mania is great.
We've sold it to you as
Americana. We've sold that to you. Now,
that is a part of America. A lot of
people, myself included, I have an
addict brain. I got into
comedy. It's worked, but for years it
didn't. I started making money at 35.
I'm now 40. I've had five years of
earning money. I had a 10-year career
before that where I didn't earn any
money. Didn't earn a lot of money.
It was me and Stavros performing at Joe
List's uh thing and we loved it. And by
the way, it was the most fun in the
world. So I I I don't regret any of it.
It was actually a lot of
fun. There are people that are going to
just want to take risks and do crazy
things and you know whether they pan out
or not. I was very lucky. I was lucky. I
was able to do it. I had to I wasn't you
know I didn't have to I mean uh I had a
good enough health to do it. I mean I'm
not a triathlete but I had good enough
health to do standup.
What I'm saying is
that this
idea that the stock market runs our
lives, that
chaos is
freedom, and that you have to be in a
manic state of reinventing
yourself. This
entrepreneurship horeshit that has been
sold to you as if a business is better
than a family. as if an empire is better
than truly knowing who you are as a
human being. It's essential to sell that
to you so that Larry Frink and Black
Rockck can steal
everything. And that's why they pump all
these gurus that tell you how to make
money and steal and all this [__]
And I'm not against money and I love
money. And no one who says they don't
love money is uh
true. But understand where it comes
from. Donald Trump is [__] the
economy up, but he's not wrong. Those
two things are both true. I'm sorry for
you to hear that. I know a lot of people
don't want to hear it. He's he's [__]
it up right now. But he's not
wrong. If you were to look at what's
happened to the country, if you were to
look at the economic and
cultural
malaise that the working class has felt,
something has to be done. Is it
realistic to get them all back into
factories? I I don't know. I don't plan
to be I'm I'm not claiming to be an
expert here. But what I'm telling you is
at the end at the end of the day, if
Larry Frink and Black Rockck are telling
you something is good for you, you know,
the company that bought all the
houses, it's probably not.
If they're selling you freedom, but
they're giving you
instability, they're giving you chaos,
they're telling you that the gig economy
is great, there Larry Frink comes out
and says, "You should invest more money.
Don't save it. Invest it.
Gamble, give it to me. Give it to us."
us and he came out and he said
that if he's out there telling
you that you're being too
cautious or responsible with your
money, you know there's a reason for it.